[{"answer": "It's not a good habit if it makes you pick fights", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "We like Second Lieutenants here", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "The freight building burned down with the uniforms! I'm not operating a fire department", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What does", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You didn't tell me your husband's name", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "But they will", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Where do you want to start", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Like for instance", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "They don't need to when they shoot so often", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "With certain exceptions", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Like my friend..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I thought we might get to that", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I knew her husband", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I knew her husband", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Considering what", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Because you're no good. And good women like men who are bad for them", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Fooling with her will get you nowhere too", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "This hotel is no good. The service is bad. The clerk's a poet, and the mattress is not quite as soft as a marble slab. But I'm beginning to like it... and if I open this window, and hear you singing..", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "That's the way", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Then I think I got a little better right than you to be there", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What are we gonna do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I'm on commission. With me it's a matter of money", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I can't think of anything else", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "We risk him, that's all", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "He don't look any worse than the rest of it looks right now.  Come on, get this junk out", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "That's a gear box you're hauling back and it's got to be repaired. And you tell my friend that if it ain't repaired we might have to shut down quick. You got that", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "All right", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "We'd given you up for dead", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Who", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I can see you have", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I can see you have", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I do", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Meaning you don't trust me", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Where do you want it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " And while we're on the subject, who does my friend represent", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I know perfectly well he's a scoundrel too.  Is he also trying to help me", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "That's right", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "We're doing something", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "A cut", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I ran one on you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "He can't think very clearly in the presence of a gun", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " No, it doesn't", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "So it boils down to thi", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Unless you also have something on me", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "You know, I think he will", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "The poorhouses are filled with careful men...  ...And so are the graveyards", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "How did you get away", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "You never said it to me", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I seem to always end up like this with you. I take you for granted. You like it that way. It goes with loaded dice and crimped cards and fixed wheels", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "It isn't my life", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Fifty thousand dollars", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Well, you see, I don't", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I thought you were in jail", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "You're a very glib man. You seem to talk your way out of everything", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "No... she had a gun with her", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "The one she had was in her hand", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "my friend might have killed you, but you fought him with your fists. The sheriff had a gun but you took it away from him. my friend had a gun last night but it didn't seem to scare you. Now this genteol petticoat waves a pistol and you run for your life", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Or I make it sound like what it i", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Why? Did Haven", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Then I don't understand", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Who did", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "You know", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "From the first night and the first time of the song. I tried to get away from it, but every time it came back. Every time I tried to get it out of my brain I just pushed it deeper into my heart. It had to be either you or me", "docId": "Station-West.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": " I love you", "qsentId": 66}]